Good morning.
Morikawa...
Morning.
I'm fine with receiving half of whatever Mai gets.
Just please, fall in love with me.
Just so you know,
I'm not so half-hearted woman that I'll avoid you after rejection.
In fact, I haven't given up.
Yeah, I still feel vexed.
Despite freaking out?
I mean, it was half price!
[Lodging for love, at half the price]
And so you didn't have sex?
Imagine my first time to be at "half-price"...
What's "half-price"?
Well... uh...
[Bang!]
[Ai-Chan's Secret | Episode 6]
That sounds real troublesome.
It's not broken, I just have to take a break from extracurriculars.
I'm really sorry!
I'm just glad you weren't hurt, Kasumi.
Whoa, what's with his suaveness?
A sudden break must be inconvenient.
Oh my gosh!
How will you all take responsibility?
- I'll be fine.
- But...
I'll...
- I'll take care of him.
- What?
Until he heals, I'll take responsibility.
- No, thank you.
- Actually,
- that'd be helpful.
- What?
I can take care of you —
Watching Kasumi be a gofer sounds fun.
Is this a new couple I see?
- Get on with it.
- Dude, what the hell?
That's dangerous, he's injured.
- Are you... mad?
- I'm not.
I can't just leave him be, it was my fault.
A "thank you" would've been enough.
I guess, but...
How nice of you.
You're full of openings.
Don't be alone with Takumi.
Okay.
Aiko, you're mine.
[Kafuu High School]
[Class Duty: Matsuda, Morikawa]
Holy moly,
is this love?
Perhaps it's already blossomed?
[Oolong Tea]
You're babying him.
It can't be helped.
He's not a kid.
You're too worried, Takumi is just a friend.
Thanks.
A "friend", huh?
I... might like her.
Those two suit one another.
No, they look like siblings.
-  Pissed that your toy's being stolen?
- Huh?
Of course not.
- Is Reo here?
- No, but I am.
I was going to eat lunch with him...
You're like a baby.
Leave it.
Want to eat with me?
- I'll have to pass.
- I see.
That was a quick rejection.
- Thanks for the food.
- Can I return the tray?
- Be right back.
- Thanks.
Seems like you're having fun.
You like that tomboy, don't you?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry,
for a lot of things.
Takumi, you're free to fall in love with whomever you want.
What about you?
- Do you still like Reo?
- Yes, I do.
But I'll control my love, so he doesn't come to dislike me.
That's why I want you to concentrate on your own love life.
[Delete photo]
[Kafuu High School]
Seriously? What to do...
What's up?
It's nothing.
- Then I'll go on ahead.
- All right.
Something happen?
Nothing. Head onto practice without me.
Now I'm curious.
Kitauchi, where's Aiko?
Oh... She's at Spica.
Aren't Wednesdays their day off?
They are, but she got tasked with chores.
This too?
[Reo]
- Yeah.
- Okay.
No one's coming to help.
- They said that no one else could.
- What?
Sorry, I forgot to mention that.
Oh... I see.
You're full of openings.
Don't be alone with Takumi.
Something wrong?
No, let's finish this up quickly.
[Aiko]
- Kasumi.
- Yeah?
Doesn't suit your personality.
I'm glad.
This area has been scrunched up.
Was it?
Are you being cautious of me?
Whoa, this dress is amazing!
Why not try it on?
It wouldn't suit me.
Ritsuki said it was for you.
Seriously?
Oh, my bad.
It's for "Mai".
You look plenty cute without the wig.
So you knew that I was "Mai".
Don't worry, I have no plans on telling.
But why don't you date him as "Aiko Kasumi"?
That's because...
Is there something frisky about sharing a secret?
Or will something bad happen, from everyone knowing?
- It's none of your business.
- It is.
Because
I like you.
♫ What awaits in this battle of love? ♫
♫ It seems it won't end in a draw ♫
♫ You hated loosing, ♫
♫ So I won't let you go easy on me ♫
I like you, "Aiko Kasumi".
I've decided to be honest with myself.
Thanks to meeting you, I've changed.
♫ I make you acting like a kid with just a sweet kiss ♫
Kasumi...
I...
♫ Only I know this ♫
♫ Rather than touching, we can melt
into one another's embrace ♫
♫ I'll let you get near just to return you like a wave ♫
♫ I'll steal you away before anyone gets the chance ♫
- Are you alone?
- I am.
I confessed to Kasumi.
Not that I have any business telling someone that isn't her boyfriend.
I told you, didn't I? She's my toy.
Why not find a new one?
The hell did you say?
Why are you mad?
Aiko, let's keep this all a secret,
I won't tell anyone
until you're ready to tell everyone that you're "Mai".
What is she doing?
What? He confessed?!
Hold on, he found out about "Mai", and confessed?
That's what I've been telling you.
Kasumi, I've
never loved someone like this before.
I won't be a bother, so let me continue this crush of mine.
And you couldn't reply?
Not to accuse, but did he make you swoon?
No way! I only like Reo.
Then you have to tell that to Takumi.
You're right.
First, think about how to tell Reo about this.
Reo, listen...
Takumi confessed to me.
As if I could tell him that.
No way!
It can't be!
You left me on read, and ignored my calls.
Sorry.
It's fine.
Well, I guess it's not.
Something come up yesterday?
Yeah, I was cleaning up at Spica.
I see. With who?
I was... alone.
Ai, here's Takumi's stuff.
Let's go, Reo!
Listen, about yesterday—
Sorry,
I think Ikumi is trying to be considerate.
That's all right.
- About yesterday—
- We'll be late
for morning practice.
Come on, let's go.
You weren't against Aiko looking after your brother?
I don't like her, but I decided to cheer him on.
Cheer him on?
So you can't bother them.
This is the absolute worst.
I couldn't tell Takumi, and lied to Reo.
Ta-daa! I got this from Ritsuki.
It's an invitation to Spica's Halloween Event.
Go give it to Reo.
I'm sorry...
I lied to you.
Yesterday... Takumi
confessed to me at Spica.
I know.
What?
Takumi told me himself.
You knew, and still asked me about it?
Yeah.
What the hell? Were you testing me?
I wanted to hear it directly from you.
Don't you believe me?
I want to. Of course I do.
Then why?
That's what I want to say. Why did you lie?
I just... happened to.
You, "happened to"?
Don't "happen to" let your guard down!
- I didn't!
- That kindness of yours
is exactly what leads other men on!
Oh, really now.
Sorry for being such a nice person.
[To Reo]
[Aiko Kasumi]
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.
[Halloween Party]
[Maid Cafe | Spica]
Your joke totally failed.
For real?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Are you dressed as Mr. Tezuka? It suits you!
(T/N: Osamu Tezuka, the manga artist)
When will Reo arrive?
He probably won't.
Didn't you hand him an invitation?
Good work, you two.
Mai, a customer wants a picture with you.
On my way!
Say cheese!
- Nice Halloween!
- Nice Halloween.
We're gonna be late, not thanks to Koike.
He was definitely messing with us.
I'm sure he's just bored.
Do you have your costume ready?
Actually, I think I won't go.
- Why?
- I forgot my costume,
and I'm in the middle of a fight with Mai.
Then you really have to go. Here, I'll lend you my costume.
- No, it's fine.
- Let's go, let's go!
- I said it's fine!
- Just take it!
You'll be fine, it'll suit you!
I hope Reo comes.
I'm not waiting for him.
You totally are.
It's freezing out there.
Mai, what should I do...?
Oh, my goodness!
C-Come right this way.
We only have costumes. Would you like to change?
- For now, I'll bring—
- Mai...
Yes?
W-We're alone.
Yes, we are.
Well...
I've always... Mai!
- What are you doing?! Stop it! Someone!
- Mai!
Reo! Stop it!
What the hell are you doing?!
I'll report you.
Y-You're wrong... N-No...
I'm sorry!
Are you okay?
Your arm is all healed up.
Just be honest, and say "thank you".
Here.
You must have been so scared. Your legs gave out.
I'm fine.
- Let me go—
- I'm so glad
that you're all right.
[Next time]
Love that begins from friendship isn't so bad.
Do you understand the implications of coming to a guy's room?
You two were finally alone...
Men are creatures who cheat.
Why not tail Reo?
I'll protect this promise between men.
There's something going on between them.